{"test_questions": [[{"question": "If a denormalization situation exists with a one-to-one binary relationship, which of the following is true?", "opta": "All fields are stored in one relation.", "optb": "All fields are stored in two relations.", "optc": "All fields are stored in three relations.", "optd": "All fields are stored in four relations.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Selecting a data type involves which of the following?", "opta": "Maximize storage space", "optb": "Represent most values", "optc": "Improve data integrity", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the best data type definition for Oracle when a field is alphanumeric and has a length that can vary?", "opta": "VARCHAR2", "optb": "CHAR", "optc": "LONG", "optd": "NUMBER", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If a denormalization situation exists with a many-to-many or associative binary relationship, which of the following is true?", "opta": "All fields are stored in one relation.", "optb": "All fields are stored in two relations.", "optc": "All fields are stored in three relations.", "optd": "All fields are stored in four relations.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is an advantage of partitioning?", "opta": "Complexity", "optb": "Inconsistent access speed", "optc": "Extra space", "optd": "Security", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The blocking factor is:", "opta": "a group of fields stored in adjacent memory.", "optb": "the number of physical records per page.", "optc": "attributes grouped together by the same primary key.", "optd": "attributes grouped together by the same secondary key.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following improves a query's processing time?", "opta": "Write complex queries.", "optb": "Combine a table with itself.", "optc": "Query one query within another.", "optd": "Use compatible data types.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following are integrity controls that a DBMS may support?", "opta": "Assume a default value in a field unless a user enters a value for that field.", "optb": "Limit the set of permissible values that a field may assume.", "optc": "Limit the use of null values in some fields.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a factor to consider when switching from small to large block size?", "opta": "The length of all of the fields in a table row.", "optb": "The number of columns", "optc": "Block contention", "optd": "Random row access speed", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the best data type definition for Oracle when a field is alphanumeric and has a fixed length?", "opta": "VARCHAR2", "optb": "CHAR", "optc": "LONG", "optd": "NUMBER", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A secondary key is which of the following?", "opta": "Nonunique key", "optb": "Primary key", "optc": "Useful for denormalization decisions", "optd": "Determines the tablespace required", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The fastest read/write time and most efficient data storage of any disk array type is:", "opta": "RAID-0.", "optb": "RAID-1.", "optc": "RAID-2.", "optd": "RAID-3.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A rule of thumb for choosing indexes for a relational database includes which of the following?", "opta": "Indexes are more useful on smaller tables.", "optb": "Indexes are more useful for columns that do not appear frequently in the WHERE clause in queries.", "optc": "Do not specify a unique index for the primary key of each table.", "optd": "Be careful indexing attributes that have null values.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Sequential retrieval on a primary key for sequential file storage has which of the following features?", "opta": "Very fast", "optb": "Moderately fast", "optc": "Slow", "optd": "Impractical", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A multidimensional database model is used most often in which of the following models?", "opta": "Data warehouse", "optb": "Relational", "optc": "Hierarchical", "optd": "Network", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}